Perls Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Negatives, circa 1937-1995, Series 2:; (Boxes 44-59; 15.7 linear feet)
  - P5891-5900 (Box 53, Folder 75)
  - P5901-5910 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - P5911-5920 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - P5921-5930 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - P5931-5940 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - P5941-5950 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - P5951-5960 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - P5961-5970 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - P5971-5980 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - P5981-5990 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - P5991-6000 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - P6001-6010 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - P6011-6020 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - P6021-6030 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - P6031-6040 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - P6041-6050 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - P6051-6060 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - P6061-6070 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - P6071-6080 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - P6081-6090 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - P6091-6100 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - P6101-6110 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - P6111-6120 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - P6121-6130 (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - P6131-6140 (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - P6141-6150 (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - P6151-6160 (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - P6161-6170 (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - P6171-6180 (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - P6181-6190 (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - P6191-6200 (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - P6201-6210 (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - P6211-6220 (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - P6221-6230 (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - P6231-6240 (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - P6241-6250 (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - P6251-6260 (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - P6261-6272 (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - P6273-6280 (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - P6281-6290 (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - P6291-6300 (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - P6301-6310 (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - P6311-6320 (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - P6321-6330 (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - P6331-6340 (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - P6341-6350 (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - P6351-6360 (Box 54, Folder 46)
  - P6361-6370 (Box 54, Folder 47)
  - P6371-6380 (Box 54, Folder 48)
  - P6381-6390 (Box 54, Folder 49)
  - P6391-6400 (Box 54, Folder 50)
  - P6401-6410 (Box 54, Folder 51)
  - P6411-6420 (Box 54, Folder 52)
  - P6421-6430 (Box 54, Folder 53)
  - P6431-6440 (Box 54, Folder 54)
  - P6441-6450 (Box 54, Folder 55)
  - P6415-6460 (Box 54, Folder 56)
  - P6461-6470 (Box 54, Folder 57)
  - P6471-6480 (Box 54, Folder 58)
  - P6481-6490 (Box 54, Folder 59)
  - P6491-6500 (Box 54, Folder 60)
  - P6501-6510 (Box 54, Folder 61)
  - P6511-6520 (Box 54, Folder 62)
  - P6521-6530 (Box 54, Folder 63)
  - P6531-6540 (Box 54, Folder 64)
  - P6541-6550 (Box 54, Folder 65)
  - P6551-6560 (Box 54, Folder 66)
  - P6561-6570 (Box 54, Folder 67)
  - P6571-6580 (Box 54, Folder 68)
  - P6581-6590 (Box 54, Folder 69)
  - P6591-6600 (Box 54, Folder 70)
  - P6601-6610 (Box 54, Folder 71)
  - P6611-6620 (Box 54, Folder 72)
  - P6621-6630 (Box 54, Folder 73)
  - P6631-6640 (Box 54, Folder 74)
  - P6641-6650 (Box 54, Folder 75)
  - P6651-6660 (Box 54, Folder 76)
  - P6661-6670 (Box 54, Folder 77)
  - P6671-6680 (Box 54, Folder 78)
  - P6681-6690 (Box 54, Folder 79)
  - P6691-6700 (Box 54, Folder 80)
  - P6701-6710 (Box 54, Folder 81)
  - P6711-6720 (Box 54, Folder 82)
  - P6721-6730 (Box 54, Folder 83)
  - P6731-6740 (Box 54, Folder 84)
  - P6741-6750 (Box 54, Folder 85)
  - P6751-6760 (Box 54, Folder 86)
  - P6761-6770 (Box 54, Folder 87)
  - P6771-6780 (Box 54, Folder 88)
  - P7001-7032 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - P7033-7041 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - P7042-7050 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - P7051-7059 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - P7060-7079 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - P7080-7099 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - P7100-7111 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - P7112-7137 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - P7138-7158 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - P7159-7182 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - P7183-7192 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - P7194-7225 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - P7226-7245 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - P7246-7262 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - P7263-7281 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - P7282-7310 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - P7311-7321 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - P7322-7335 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - P7336-7347 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - P7348-7357 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - P7358-7380 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - P7381-7418 (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - P7419-7448 (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - P7449-7454 (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - P7455-7484 (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - P7485-7510 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - P7511-8538 (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - P7539-7550 (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - P7551-7566 (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - P7567-7575 (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - P7576-7586 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - P7587-7590 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - P7591-7612 (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - P7613-7620 (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - P7621-7634 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - P7635-7664 (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - P7665-7692 (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - P7693-7711 (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - P7716-7718 (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - P7719-7733 (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - P7734-7783 (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - P7784-7785 (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - P7786-7807 (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - P7808-7817 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - P7818-7828 (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - P7829-7851 (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - P7852-7864 (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - P7865-7878 (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - P7879-7889 (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - P7890-7917 (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - P7918-7932 (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - P7933-7942 (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - P7943-7954 (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - P7955-7958 (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - P7959-7973 (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - P7974-7987 (Box 55, Folder 56)
  - P7988-8005 (Box 55, Folder 57)
  - P8006-8016 (Box 55, Folder 58)
  - P8017-8030 (Box 55, Folder 59)
  - P8031-8041 (Box 55, Folder 60)
  - P8042-8053 (Box 55, Folder 61)
  - P8054-8075 (Box 55, Folder 62)
  - P8076-8099 (Box 55, Folder 63)
  - P8100-8115 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - P8116-8126 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - P8127-8134 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - P8135-8144 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - P8145-8153 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - P8154-8169 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - P8170-8181 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - P8182-8195 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - P8196-8199 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - P8200-8219 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - P8220-8234 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - P8235-8243 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - P8244-8255 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - P8256-8265 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - P8266-8276 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - P8277-8287 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - P8288-8298 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - P8299-8306 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - P8307-8329 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - P8330-8351 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - P8352-8362 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - P8363-8380 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - P8381-8404 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - P8405-8409 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - P8410-8423 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - P8424-8433 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - P8434-8447 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - P8448-8457 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - P8458-8470 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - P8471-8485 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - P8486-8502 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - P8503-8521 (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - P8522-8535 (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - P8536-8541 (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - P8542-8555 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - P8556-8561 (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - P8563-8568 (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - P8569-8578 (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - P8579-8589 (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - P8592-8613 (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - P8614-8622 (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - P8624-8629 (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - P8630-8660 (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - P8661-8671 (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - P8672-8694 (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - P8695-8706 (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - P8707-8720 (Box 56, Folder 47)
  - P8721-8733 (Box 56, Folder 48)
  - P8734-8744 (Box 56, Folder 49)
  - P8745-8754 (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - P8755-8759 (Box 56, Folder 51)
  - P8760-8777 (Box 56, Folder 52)
  - P8778-8785 (Box 56, Folder 53)
  - P8786-8798 (Box 56, Folder 54)
  - P8799-8806 (Box 56, Folder 55)
  - P8807-8816 (Box 56, Folder 56)
  - P8817-8830 (Box 56, Folder 57)
  - P8831-8843 (Box 56, Folder 58)
  - P8844-8854 (Box 56, Folder 59)
  - P8855-8862 (Box 56, Folder 60)
  - P8863-8876 (Box 56, Folder 61)
  - P8877-8887 (Box 56, Folder 62)
  - P8888-8900 (Box 56, Folder 63)
  - P8901-8912 (Box 56, Folder 64)
  - P8913-8923 (Box 56, Folder 65)
  - P8924-8937 (Box 56, Folder 66)
  - P8938-8950 (Box 56, Folder 67)
  - P8951-8959 (Box 56, Folder 68)
  - P8960-8969 (Box 56, Folder 69)
  - P8972-8981 (Box 56, Folder 70)
  - P8982-8996 (Box 56, Folder 71)
  - P8997-9007 (Box 56, Folder 72)
  - P9008-9019 (Box 56, Folder 73)
  - P9020-9037 (Box 56, Folder 74)
  - P9038-9054 (Box 56, Folder 75)
  - P9055-9065 (Box 56, Folder 76)
  - P9066-9075 (Box 56, Folder 77)
  - P9076-9086 (Box 56, Folder 78)
  - P9087-9096 (Box 56, Folder 79)
  - P9097-9114 (Box 56, Folder 80)
  - P9115-9125 (Box 56, Folder 81)
  - P9126-9140 (Box 56, Folder 82)
  - P9141-9150 (Box 56, Folder 83)
  - P9151-9164 (Box 56, Folder 84)
  - P9165-9177 (Box 56, Folder 85)
  - P9178-9192 (Box 56, Folder 86)
  - P9193-9205 (Box 56, Folder 87)
  - P9206-9220 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - P9221-9228 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - P9229-9238 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - P9245-9258 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - P9258-9267 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - P9268-9277 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - P9278-9287 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - P9289-9297 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - P9298-9310 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - P9311-9322 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - P9323-9333 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - P9334-9347 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - P9348-9357 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - P9358-9371 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - P9372-9383 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - P9384-9395 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - P9396-9406 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - P9407-9420 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - P9421-9431 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - P9432-9442 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - P9443-9456 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - P9458-9467 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - P9469-9481 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - P9482-9495 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - P9496-9506 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - P9507-9516 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - P9517-9529 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - P9530-9540 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - P9541-9551 (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - P9552-9563 (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - P9564-9574 (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - P9575-9585 (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - P9586-9594 (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - P9595-9606 (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - P9607-9619 (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - P9620-9629 (Box 57, Folder 36)
  - P9630-9639 (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - P9640-9649 (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - P9650-9659 (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - P9660-9669 (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - P9670-9679 (Box 57, Folder 41)
  - P9680-9689 (Box 57, Folder 42)
  - P9690-9699 (Box 57, Folder 43)
  - P9700-9709 (Box 57, Folder 44)
  - P9710-9719 (Box 57, Folder 45)
  - P9720-9729 (Box 57, Folder 46)
  - P9730-9739 (Box 57, Folder 47)
  - P9740-9749 (Box 57, Folder 48)
  - P9750-9759 (Box 57, Folder 49)
  - P9760-9769 (Box 57, Folder 50)
  - P9770-9779 (Box 57, Folder 51)
  - P9780-9789 (Box 57, Folder 52)
  - P9791-9799 (Box 57, Folder 53)
  - P9800-9810 (Box 57, Folder 54)
  - P9811-9820 (Box 57, Folder 55)
  - P9821-9830 (Box 57, Folder 56)
  - P9831-9840 (Box 57, Folder 57)
  - P9841-9850 (Box 57, Folder 58)
  - P9851-9860 (Box 57, Folder 59)
  - P9861-9870 (Box 57, Folder 60)
  - P9871-9880 (Box 57, Folder 61)
  - P9881-9890 (Box 57, Folder 62)
  - P9891-9900 (Box 57, Folder 63)
  - P9901-9910 (Box 57, Folder 64)
  - P9911-9920 (Box 57, Folder 65)
  - P9921-9930 (Box 57, Folder 66)
  - P9931-9940 (Box 57, Folder 67)
  - P9941-9950 (Box 57, Folder 68)
  - P9951-9960 (Box 57, Folder 69)
  - P9961-9970 (Box 57, Folder 70)
  - P9971-9980 (Box 57, Folder 71)
  - P9981-9990 (Box 57, Folder 72)
  - P9991-10000 (Box 57, Folder 73)
  - P10001-10010 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - P10011-10020 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - P10021-10030 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - P10031-10040 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - P10041-10050 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - P10051-10060 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - P10061-10070 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - P10071-10080 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - P10081-10090 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - P10091-10100 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - P10101-10110 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - P10111-10120 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - P10121-10130 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - P10131-10140 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - P10141-10142 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Calder P1914-2487 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Calder P2496-2654 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Calder P2705-2743 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Calder P2744-2868 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Calder P2870-2915 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Calder P2916-2948 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Calder P2954-2975 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Calder P2977-3065 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Calder P3066-3094 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Calder P3097-3187 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Calder P3188-3305 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Calder P3306-3324 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Calder P3326-3398 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Calder P3399-3434 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Calder P3447-3534 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Calder P3538-3617 (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Calder P3619-3659 (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Calder P3664-3693 (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Calder P3698-3750 (Box 58, Folder 34)
  - Calder P3752-3787 (Box 58, Folder 35)
  - Calder P3788-3903 (Box 58, Folder 36)
  - Calder P3908-3950 (Box 58, Folder 37)
  - Calder P3953-3972 (Box 58, Folder 38)
  - Calder P3974-4016 (Box 58, Folder 39)
  - Calder P4017-4071 (Box 58, Folder 40)
  - Calder P4073-4150 (Box 58, Folder 41)
  - Calder P4151-4167 (Box 58, Folder 42)
  - Calder P4172-4245 (Box 58, Folder 43)
  - Calder P4246-4311 (Box 58, Folder 44)
  - Calder P4322-4379 (Box 58, Folder 45)
  - Calder P4400-4438 (Box 58, Folder 46)
  - Calder P4462-4499 (Box 58, Folder 47)
  - Calder P4510-4595 (Box 58, Folder 48)
  - Calder P4613-1647 (Box 58, Folder 49)
  - Calder P4650-4705 (Box 58, Folder 50)
  - Calder P4706-4718 (Box 58, Folder 51)
  - Calder P4720-4816 (Box 58, Folder 52)
  - Calder P4817-4891 (Box 58, Folder 53)
  - Calder P4892-4934 (Box 58, Folder 54)
  - Calder P4935-4997 (Box 58, Folder 55)
  - Calder P4998-5040 (Box 58, Folder 56)
  - Calder P5045-5109 (Box 58, Folder 57)
  - Calder P5117-5221 (Box 58, Folder 58)
  - Calder P5227-5305 (Box 58, Folder 59)
  - Calder P5313-5383 (Box 58, Folder 60)
  - Calder P5385-5415 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Calder P5422-5507 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Calder P5508-5550 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Calder P5557-5594 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Calder P5597-5678 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Calder P5680-5715 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Calder P5716-5811 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Calder P5824-5925 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Calder P5926-5967 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Calder P5975-6021 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Calder P6022-6056 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Calder P6059-6131 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Calder P6139-6179 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Calder P6213-6230 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Calder P6233-6295 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Calder P6310-6340 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Calder P6352-6405 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Calder P6407-6438 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Calder P6455-6481 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Calder P6521-6537 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Calder P6555-6599 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Calder P6619-6648 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Calder P6652-6698 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Calder P6718-6778 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Old Negative Numbers 3/1313-6709 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Old Negative Numbers 6744-6868 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Old Negative Numbers 6885-6896 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Old Negative Numbers 7106-7138 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Old Negative Numbers 7172-7288 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Old Negative Numbers 7303-7310 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Old Negative Numbers 7322-7343 (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Old Negative Numbers 7345-7378 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Old Negatives, Unnumbered (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - Old Negatives, Unknown (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - Index Cards, (index card box) (Box 59, Folder 35)
- Photographs, circa 1937-1995, Series 3:; (Boxes 60-75, OV 84; 16.1 linear feet)
  Photographs in this series depict mostly artwork of gallery inventory, and a smaller amount of non-gallery artwork. Filed within the gallery inventory photographs are also photographs of installations, and occasional correspondence related to particular images. Provenance, sales, and exhibition records found interfiled with related photographs have been left in place. Also found are twenty-seven folders of photographs of artists. Most of the photographs are black and white and many are filed along with slides or transparencies.
  The photographs are arranged into three subseries:
  Subseries 1: Artists, circa 1937-1995
  Subseries 2: Inventory, circa 1937-1995
  Subseries 3: Artist Files, circa 1937-1995
  - Artists, circa 1937-1995, 3.1
    Found here are black and white and color photographs of artists, most of which are portraits. Many of the images are attributed to Alfredo Valente. The photographs are arranged alphabetically by artist. For photographs of Alexander Calder, see Box 13, Folder 51 (Fleiss, Marcel) and Box 30, Folder 22 (Newsweek Magazine).
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 1959 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Austin, Darrel, 1978 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Austin, Margot, circa 1950 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Blanchard, Carol, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Belle, Narcisse, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Brisset, Marcel, circa 1945 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Bombois, Camille, circa 1940 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Calder, Alexander, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Carreño, Mario, circa 1945 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Chagall, Marc, 1965 (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Dufy, Raoul, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Friedman, Martin, circa 1955 (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Glasco, Joseph, 1950 (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - Haucke, Frederick, circa 1940 (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - La More, Chet, circa 1940 (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Martinez-Pedro, Luis, circa 1945 (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Masteller, John R., circa 1945 (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Papsdorf, Frederick, circa 1950 (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Pascin, Julescirca 1900 (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Pereng, Madeleine, undated (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Peyronnet, Dominique Paul, circa 1920 (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - Priebe, Karl, circa 1948, (see also Box 80, Folder 5) (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Stark, Margaret, circa 1945 (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, circa 1965 (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - Tschabasov, Nahum, circa 1950 (Box 60, Folder 25)
    - Wilson, Reginald, circa 1940 (Box 60, Folder 26)
    - Unidentified, 1944 (Box 60, Folder 27)
    - Unidentified, circa 1945 (Box 60, Folder 28)
    - Unidentified, 1956 (Box 60, Folder 29)
    - Priebe, Karl, undated, (see also Box 60, Folder 22) (Box 80 (sol), Folder 5)
  - Inventory, circa 1937-1995, 3.2
    This series is comprised primarily of photographs of artwork in Perls Galleries', including installation views and the occasional letter.
    Photographs of inventory are arranged in two groups: Artwork and Objects Sold, both arranged alphabetically by artist, geographical region, or tribe, and then by stock number. The index cards described at the end of Series 2 can provide stock number access to the photographs.
    Dates provided on the folders refer to the dates of the artwork depicted in each image rather than to the dates the photographes were taken.
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 4000-4539, 1910-1958 (Box 60, Folder 30)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 6567-8149, 1910-1963 (Box 60, Folder 31)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 8152-8652, 1909-1962 (Box 60, Folder 32)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 9127-9288, 1908-1963 (Box 60, Folder 33)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 9289-1193, 1912-1954 (Box 60, Folder 34)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 12000-12755, 1913-1959 (Box 60, Folder 35)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 12820-13097, 1912-1963 (Box 60, Folder 36)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 7700-12983, 1917-1963 (Box 60, Folder 37)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 13002-13251, 1910-1963 (Box 60, Folder 38)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 13307-13339, 1916-1948 (Box 60, Folder 39)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 13340-13452, 1912-1918 (Box 60, Folder 40)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 13457-13519, 1912-1920 (Box 60, Folder 41)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 13526-13541, 1912-1921 (Box 60, Folder 42)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 13594-13659, 1917-1963 (Box 60, Folder 43)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 13662-13705, 1912-1956 (Box 60, Folder 44)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 13714-13784, 1910-1935 (Box 60, Folder 45)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, 13803-13842, 1909-1954 (Box 60, Folder 46)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, His Negatives, 1914-1915 (Box 60, Folder 47)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, His Negatives, 1909-1954 (Box 60, Folder 48)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, His Negatives, 1914-1957 (Box 60, Folder 49)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, Not Our Negatives, 1912-1975 (Box 60, Folder 50)
    - Archipenko, Alexander, Not Our Negatives, 1921-1975 (Box 60, Folder 51)
    - Austin, Darrel, 725-729, 1928-1944 (Box 60, Folder 52)
    - Austin, Darrel, 732-1179, 1940-1943 (Box 60, Folder 53)
    - Austin, Darrel, 1180-1419, 1937-1944 (Box 60, Folder 54)
    - Austin, Darrel, 1459-1492, 1940-1941 (Box 60, Folder 55)
    - Austin, Darrel, 1501-1961, 1941-1944 (Box 60, Folder 56)
    - Austin, Darrel, 1988-2193, 1944-1945 (Box 60, Folder 57)
    - Austin, Darrel, 2202-2729, 1945-1946 (Box 60, Folder 58)
    - Austin, Darrel, 2796-2848, 1946-1947 (Box 60, Folder 59)
    - Austin, Darrel, 2857-2990, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 60)
    - Austin, Darrel, 3001-3740, 1937-1948 (Box 60, Folder 61)
    - Austin, Darrel, 3741-3832, 1948-1949 (Box 60, Folder 62)
    - Austin, Darrel, 3874-3930, 1942-1950 (Box 60, Folder 63)
    - Austin, Darrel, 3931-3990, 1944-1951 (Box 60, Folder 64)
    - Austin, Darrel, 1993-4000, 1951 (Box 60, Folder 65)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4001-4026, 1938-1952 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4028-4050, 1950-1952 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4052-4075, 1952-1953 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4076-4098, 1951-1954 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4130-4198, 1955 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4301-4382, 1951-1957 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4383-4410, 1957 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4413-4444, 1957-1958 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4445-4477, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4478-4485, 1958 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4501-4537, 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4540-4556, 1958-1959 (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4557-4565, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Austin, Darrel, 4856-7436, 1940-1964 (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - Austin, Darrel, 7986-8000, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Austin, Darrel, 8001-8033, 1959 (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Austin, Darrel, 8034-8112, 1945-1959 (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Austin, Darrel, 8161-8186, 1944-1960 (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Austin, Darrel, 8201-8219, 1960 (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Austin, Darrel, 8253-8284, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Austin, Darrel, 8297-8320, 1944-1961 (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - Austin, Darrel, 8321-8340, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - Austin, Darrel, 8371-8420, 1959-1961 (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - Austin, Darrel, 8601-8678, 1958-1965 (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - Austin, Darrel, 8761-8910, 1961-1963 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Austin, Darrel, 8911-8920, 1961-1963 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Austin, Darrel, 8921-8933, 1962-1964 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Austin, Darrel, 11619-12544, 1960-1978 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Austin, Darrel, 12546-12571, 1965-1978 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Austin, Darrel, 12541-12602, 1968-1975 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Austin, Darrel, 12572-12642, 1958-1975 (Box 61, Folder 31)
    - Austin, Darrel, 12600-13200, 1947-1973 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Austin, Darrel, 12643-13059, 1956-1979 (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Austin, Darrel, 13061-13488, 1942-1973 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Austin, Darrel, Austins to Meek, 728-2122, 1935-1945 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Austin, Darrel, Austins to Meek, 2512-4071, 1946-1953 (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Austin, Darrel, Austins to Meek, 4086-8336, 1954-1961 (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - Austin, Darrel, Austins to Meek, 8338-8922, 1961-1963 (Box 61, Folder 38)
    - Austin, Darrel, Austins to Meek, 12545-12567, 1959-1978 (Box 61, Folder 39)
    - Austin, Darrel, Austins to Meek, 12579-12630, 1964-1974 (Box 61, Folder 40)
    - Austin, Darrel, Austins to Meek, 12631-12645, 1968-1974 (Box 61, Folder 41)
    - Austin, Darrel, Austins to Meek, 12667-12709, 1954-1973 (Box 61, Folder 42)
    - Austin, Darrel, Austins to Meek, 13054-13059, 1962-1973 (Box 61, Folder 43)
    - Austin, Darrel, Austins to Meek, 13060-13159, 1972-1975 (Box 61, Folder 44)
    - Austin, Darrel, Austins to Meek, 13160-13177, 1939-1972 (Box 61, Folder 45)
    - Austin, Darrel, Austins to Meek, 13252-13265, 1964-1973 (Box 61, Folder 46)